

Le Hoa

Front-End Developer

Date of birth: 24/01/1999

Gender: Male

Phone: 0334517232

Email: lehoa08121998@gmail.com

Address: Binh Ky, Hoa Quy, Ngu Hanh Son, Da Nang

Website: https://hoale240803.github.io/hoaleportfolio

OBJECTIVE

I would like to work in a professional working environment, where I can develop my professional skills, learn a lot of new programming knowledge and experience to improve myself more and more, and complete the work excellently. In the next 2 years, I want to become a professional Full-stack developer. I also interesting in the script, therefore, I will learn how to apply automation skills like DevOps into my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 Capstone Project

Overview: Translation Social Network Website

Team size: 4 member.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, ReactJs, ASP.NET Core 3.1, Mysql, MongoDB, Docker, Gitlab, Elastic Search Engine, Solr Search Engine.

Jan 2020 - Jun 2020 Developer and Tester FPT Software Da Nang

Overview: Moving from Flex to Angular.

Team size: 10 member.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Angular.

SKILLS

Front-End	ReactJs, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Angular.

Back-End Java, C # (.NET Core), Python, JavaScripts, NodeJs.

Database MongoDB, Mysql, Microsoft Sql Server, MariaDB.

Subversion Github, Git Lab, SVN, Azure DevOps

Cloud computing Firebase, AWS.

EDUCATION

Oct 2017 - Oct 2021 Graduated from Da Nang FPT University.

Major: BrSE (Bridge Software Engineer)

GPA: 3.0/4